infinitecampus.com 2015-10-27

# Privacy Policy

                                                         Privacy Policy
                                                         Thank you for visiting Infinite Campus. Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy has been compiled to better
                                                         serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US
                                                         privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact,
                                                         or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear under-
                                                         standing of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your PII.
                                                         What does this Privacy Policy cover?
                                                         This privacy policy is only for the website (www.infinitecampus.com), blog, (blog.infinitecampus.com) and related publicly
                                                         accessible content and does not pertain to Infinite Campus product offerings such as our Student Information System, Learn-
                                                         ing Management System, or any other fee-based offering. If the offering requires a username and password to access it, it will
                                                         generally have its own Privacy Policy.
                                                         What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?
                                                         Infinite Campus does not collect PII about you, unless you provide information to us, which is voluntary. When providing
                                                         PII, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, job title and other
                                                         details to help assist in your experience with Infinite Campus.
                                                         When do we collect information?
                                                         We collect information through such methods as signing up for an online demo or event, subscribing to a newsletter, re-
                                                         sponding to a survey, filling out a contact form.
                                                         How do we use your information?
                                                         We may use your information voluntarily provided to us to: (a) provide better, personalized service in responding to your cus-
                                                         tomer service requests, (b) communicate with you regarding specific products and services, (c) process your service requests,
                                                         (d) help improve our website (e) to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
                                                         How do we protect visitor information?
                                                         We do not share or sell your data with any other vendors or third parties. All personal information you provide is contained
                                                         behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who are required to keep the information
                                                         confidential. In addition, any information you supply via forms on our site is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL)
                                                         technology.
                                                         Do we use ‘cookies’?
                                                         Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser
                                                         (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember cer-
                                                         tain information.
                                                         We use cookies to:
                                                         1. Understand a user’s preferences and the types of information about our products and services they may be interested in.
                                                         2. Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the
                                                         future. We may also use trusted third party services such as Google Analytics that track this information on our behalf.
                                                         You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies.
                                                         You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s
                                                         Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
© 2013 Infinite Campus, Inc. All Rights Reserved. 2.15
                                                         If you choose to disable cookies, some features might not function properly.
                                                         Third Party Disclosure
                                                         We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you
                                                         with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website,
                                                         conducting our business, or servicing you, however, those parties have agreed to keep this information confidential. We may
                                                         also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or
                                                         protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.
                                                                              4321 109th Avenue NE >> Blaine, MN 55449 >> 800 850 2335 >>   Transforming K12 Education®

How does our site handle “do not track” signals?
We do not honor “do not track” (DNT) signals because we do not track our users or utilize third-party behavioral tracking.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can
Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email to stop receiving emails from Infinite Campus.
Contact Information
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
Infinite Campus
4321 109th Ave NE
Blaine, MN 55449
Email: info@infinitecampus.com
Phone: 1.800.850.2335
